Autumn is here.
The cultural festival is over, and now
we're preparing for the athletic festival.
October 17th
(Mon.)
Athletic
Festival
Teams
Relay
Inuzuka
Shikimori
Scavenger Hunt Race
Nagumo
Taneda
Henna
Boys & Girls
Mixed Relay
Okay, that takes care of
the scavenger hunt race.
Next up is... the boys and girls mixed relay.
And since nobody's volunteered...
We'll pick the runners by lottery.
Okay, line up.
I won't be of any help,
so I hope I get an event
that's not a big deal.
With a lottery, you know
it's gonna end up being Izumi.
Poor Izumi.
I haven't even drawn yet!
Boys & Girls Mixed Relay
You're In
It doesn't even surprise me anymore.
All is as it should be.
I saw this coming myself.
Not the relay... Not the relay...
Not the relay...
She really doesn't want this!
Please, God!
Boys & Girls Mixed Relay
You're In
Meeeeeeeelt
Athletic
Festival
Teams
Relay
Inuzuka
Shikimori
Scavenger Hunt Race
Nakajima
Muraki
Itou
Boys & Girls Mixed Relay
Izumi
Hachimitsu
So our first girl for the
relay is Hachimitsu.
Let's just try our best, okay?
Hachimitsu-san... Please get up...
Wanna trade?
You're Out
Hachimitsu-san!
Really?!
Shh.
Tha-Thump
Izumi-san! I'm in the relay, too!
Wow, really?
She's so overprotective...
We just need one more
boy and one more girl.
Me.
I'll do it.
How come, Inuzuka-kun?
'Cause a relay with you
guys oughta be super fun!
Okay, then I'll do it, too!
You guys really are good friends, huh?
Okay, that's it for the mixed relay.
This should be a fun relay, huh, Izumi-san?
I feel so much better,
Inuzuka-kun! Thank you!
Sure! Let's show 'em what we got.
If you're gonna play the hero,
do it where he can see you.
I wasn't trying to play the hero!
Boys & Girls Mixed Relay
Izumi
Hachimitsu
Shikimori
Inuzuka
Nekozaki
What's our running order?
There's something I'd like to say first.
What?
I'm going to hold you all back.
You're just announcing that now?!
Indoorsy
Sorry... I'll do my best,
but I'll probably hold you back too.
At least Izumi's here.
That makes me feel a little better.
Nah, he's not slow or anything.
He just falls a lot.
You traitor!
D-Don't worry! It's a sure bet I'll fall!
What kind of follow-up is that?!
I don't think you need to worry so much.
Yeah.
We're—
We're here, after all!
What is with you?! Come on!
Why are you mad at me?!
Now, now.
With the five of us on the team,
I bet it's gonna make for a great memory!
I think this will be the most fun
athletic festival of my life.
How is Izumi so optimistic?
Shikimori's Not Just a Cutie
Shikimori's
Not
Just
a
Cutie
Shikimori's
Not
Just
a
Cutie
Shikimori's
Not Just a Cutie
Amusement Park
Shikimori-san might like it??
Get a reservation!!!
Get gifts for the family
Eat this!!
Inuzuka-kun
Keep warm and go to bed early!!
Inuzuka-kun!!
Please Help
I'm going to an amusement park with
Shikimori-san next week. Suggestions...?
#10  The Desire to Win
All right!
Time to practice for the
boys and girls mixed relay!
One practice isn't gonna make
slow runners any faster.
Well, let's just do everything we can!
I mean, the five of us actually
get to do this together!
We wanna win!
Yeah!
Okay, let's spread out a bit
and practice the hand-off.
Right!
Okay.
Sure!
First Leg
Nekozaki
Second Leg
Hachimitsu
Third Leg
Izumi
Fourth Leg
Shikimori
Anchor
Inuzuka
Here I come!
Here!
Trot
Her stride is way too short!
Toddle
Keep it up!
She's already worn out?!
All yours!
Why...
...the heck?!
Izumi-san!
This is hopeless.
It's never gonna work...
Here!
W-We're sorry.
As long as we nail the hand-offs,
we should be able to recover.
It looks like this order should work, too.
If you guys get passed,
Shikimori and I can make up ground.
They're so nice...
Okay! One more practice run!
Sorry. We gotta go practice
for our other events.
I guess that's it for us today.
Okay.
Be careful.
Hachimitsu-san...
What?
If you want, well...
We could practice a little longer.
Yeah. We should.
Here.
We're... doing a lot better
than that first time.
Yeah...
Let's take a little break.
Hachimitsu-san...
What?
Eep!
I just... wanted to thank you
for practicing with me.
You're not overdoing it, are you?
I'm at my limit...
Sorry.
But...
I didn't stay to practice for you.
I'm doing it for myself.
But it didn't seem like
you wanted to practice.
Relax.
I'm always this lethargic.
I hate running because it's not
like you get anything out of doing it.
But this time...
It's making you guys happy.
So even if it wears me out,
it's still good for me.
Hachimitsu-san!
You have so much energy.
Yeah!
I envy you.
Put your jacket on.
Okay!
Athletic Festival
Phoenix
Blue Dragon
Golden Tiger
Our 44th athletic festival will now begin.
Entrance
Neko, your hair looks so nice!
The day is finally upon us!
You think so?
It's time to show off the results
of our intensive practice!
I do!
Izumi! Baton!
Except...
Hmm
Hmm.
She has no drive at all!
Hachimitsu-san is actually frowning.
I have to cheer her up somehow.
Izumi, we need to head over
to the mock cavalry battle.
Huh? Er, hang on...
C'mon, let's go.
Hachimitsu.
Want to go cheer them on with us?
Sure.
Participants in the mock cavalry battle,
please assemble at area 3 inside the track.
Oh, Izumi's a horse?
Isn't being a horse gonna kill him?
Can he even lift anyone up?
Ready, and...
Wow, he's stronger than I thought.
Okay, don't break formation.
Right foot first!
"He's so cool. I love him."
D-Don't give me a voiceover!
Good try.
Man, I never would have thought
it'd turn out like that.
They lost
Thanks, Inuzuka-kun.
Don't mention it.
The next event is the girls' ball toss.
Aren't you in that, Hachimitsu-san?
Participants, please assemble
at area 5 inside the track.
I guess I could just blow it off...
Hachimitsu!
You can do it!
Think she'll be okay?
The net's so high up.
Athletic Festival
The girls' ball toss will now begin.
You can do it!
You got this!
Nothing's going in!
It's too high up!
Oh, crap!
Yeah, that's not going in.
The net's too high for girls.
What?!
W-Wow!
B-But she's slow to pick up more balls!
But they're all going in!
Nice!
Keep it up!
First place in the girls'
ball toss goes to Class 3.
In second place...
Whew, that was a good laugh!
You burned out toward the end, huh?
If you had any stamina,
you would've won.
Shut up.
Hachimitsu.
You did great.
You looked really cool!
Hachimitsu, you were seriously amazing!
You really are a riot, Hachimitsu!
Cut it out.
That smug grin!
She looks so happy!
Entrance
My hair's a mess, and I'm
covered in sand. This sucks.
But...
I guess...
This athletic festival is more fun than most.
All right, let's keep this up!
And kick butt in the relay!
Yeah!
That Afternoon
Participants in the boys and girls
mixed relay, please assemble.
Entrance
Should we say a prayer
for Izumi's shoelaces?
I repeat: participants in the
boys and girls mixed relay...
Even if we do, some other stroke
of bad luck will find him.
Rude!
He won't fall! They'll stay tied! It's fine!
Laces, stay tied! Shoes, stay on! Don't fall!
H-Hey, come on! Seriously?!
They're not the least bit nervous.
Let's do our best, Hachimitsu-san!
Yep.
Let's win.
Hey, why aren't you guys saying anything?
Well said, Hachimitsu!
She sure is motivated.
Aw, Hachimitchoo!
First runners, third runners,
and anchors, please take your places!
Okay, ready to go?
Yep.
Let's win this!
What was that all about?
Hachimitsu.
We should get moving, too.
Right.
You can do it!
Normally, I don't get
nervous about anything.
But I might puke.
Lub-dub  Lub-dub  Lub-dub  Lub-dub  Lub-dub  Lub-dub  Lub-dub
Something's already dripping out!
Give me your hand.
Yours is ice cold.
Because I'm nervous.
You?
Of course.
You don't look it at all.
That's because it doesn't matter who wins.
What matters is that we have fun.
Oh, please. You know you have
no intention of losing.
Of course!
Yikes.
Your face is scary.
Huh?!
Go for it!
Fight hard!
Class 4!
You can do it!
That's so cool. Everyone's really hyped up.
Nekozaki-san!
Go get 'em!
Yeah, okay!
Will it all work out like we planned?
Take your marks!
I'm serious about this. Because...
Set!
I really want to win!
First and second are neck and neck!
Come on, Class 1!
Hachimitsu.
It's okay.
We're all here.
I'm here.
Sorry! I couldn't break away!
All yours, Hachimitsu!
Go!
Keep it up!
Class 4!
Oh, crap...
My mind is totally blank...
H-Her face is melting!
Man... Is she worn out?
Gah, passed already?
Her stride's so long...
And I'm moving my legs faster
than I ever have before.
I seriously don't know
what's happening anymore.
Um... Right, left...
Right, le—
Huh?
That had to hurt.
H-Hachimitsu!
She went down face first.
Is she okay?
Izumi's shoelace curse
hit Hachimitsu instead!
Can that happen?!
Uh... The baton...
Oh, I still have it.
Uh...
Um, so now...
Hachimitsu-san!
Just a little farther!
It isn't like me
to talk about winning.
They all looked shocked, too.
But I can't help it.
That's where I ended up.
After all that practice,
if we manage to win...
How much will all of you smile?
Izumi...
It's all yours!
Leave it to me!
Class 4 has handed off the baton!
Keep it up!
Fourth leg runners, get ready!
Hachimitchoo!
There's a pretty big gap
between them and Class 1.
It's gonna be tough.
Doesn't look like they'll catch up.
Hey, you okay?
I hurt so bad...
And I'm even more exhausted.
Whoa, stop! Don't melt!
But the hand-off went perfectly.
In first place is Class 1!
They're moving fast!
And in sixth place is Class 4!
Hang in there!
We fell into last place,
but not by that much.
I can at least catch up to this guy!
That's it, Izumi! Please keep this up!
Of course!
This always happens, doesn't it?!
It's all yours!
No! We can't lose because of my bad luck.
Not this time!
He stayed on his feet!
Damn, he's amazing!
He kicked off both shoes at once!
I get it. His bad luck actually saved him.
Is that even possible?!
You can do it, Izumi!
Go, Class 4!
Man, he's a riot!
Anchors, stand by!
Here they come.
Hey.
What?
You look scary with that
serious face. Could you stop?
Shut up.
Also, I'm about to run.
Aren't you gonna cheer me on?
O-Oh... G-Go for it.
Yep!
It's no use. I can't pass him.
At least I didn't let the gap widen, but...
Sorry, Shikimori-san.
I wonder why it is...
Even in a tight spot like this,
I somehow believe you'll make it happen.
Win, Shikimori-san!
I can't see...
Why is everyone so excited?
Who is she?! She's so fast!
She's already up to second place!
How awesome is she?!
I don't think she's gonna catch
up to first place, though...
Damn, she kicked up the pace again.
Shikimori really is fast.
If she was chasing me,
I wonder if I could get away...
She's staring right at me!
And those eyes! If I don't win,
she's gonna kill me!
Here!
Yeah, I know.
Nekozaki made it to first
place right off the bat,
and Hachimitsu made the hand-off
just like she practiced.
Izumi didn't even fall.
And Shikimori made up the ground we'd lost.
All that's left...
Let's win.
...is for me to keep my promise.
Their anchor has the baton now!
Class 4 is making a huge comeback!
Come on.
Come on!
In first place...
Class 4!
Yes!
Inuzuka-kun!
Izumi!
We actually won.
Shikimori-san!
Everyone was watching you when
you passed the next runner!
That was so amazing! We actually won!
What do I do?! I think I'm gonna cry!
Uh... Y-Yeah...
He's way too frank...
Got Praised to High Heaven
That was really wild, huh?!
First place winners,
take this and line up, please.
Oh, okay.
We really managed to win.
Thanks.
That was fun.
I'm glad I met you guys.
You're so cute, and so cool.
You're friends I can be proud of.
SEE YOU~